# **ZACHARY SANSO**

## **SUMMARY**

I have worked every position of several restaurants and decided that I need a larger challenge in my life. I enjoy putting my brain to the test by attempting to solve large problems. I have just graduated from the data analytics program via springboard and earned my certification.

## **EDUCATION**

## **Allendale Academy**

2007 - 2011

High School Diploma 2011

**Springboard** 

Mar. 2021 - Sept. 2021

Certification Data Analytics 2021

Springboard Data Analytics Career Track, Certification 2021 6-month intensive course in data analytics technologies and methods.

### **EMPLOYMENT**

Village Grill and More, Kitchen Manager, Deland, FL	Feb. 2016 - Dec. 2016
Mulligan's Grill, Morning Kitchen Manager, Port Orange, FL	Fall 2014 - Sept. 2018
<b>Olive Garden</b> , <i>Culinary Professional/Assistant Manager</i> , Port orange, FL	Sept. 2012 - Apr. 2016
Carrabba's Italian Grill, Cook, Daytona Beach, FL	Sept. 2018 - Current

### **SKILLS**

**DATA ANALYSIS:** analytics, SQL, python, excel, powerpoint, powerBl, word, tableau, office, data visualization

COOKING:

**MATHEMATICS:** inventory, inventory management, inventory assessment, truck orders, linear regression

## **PROJECTS**

How Do I Win More Games of League of Legends?

ChemCorp Inc. Non-Technical Presentation

Capstone 1 - Have We Lost Sight of the Purpose of the Federal Minimum Wage in the United States?

**AEMR Executive Presentation**